clicksbazaar.com 2014-12-14

# Clicks Bazaar Privacy Policy -ClicksBazaar.com

Clicks Bazaar believes that strong electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial and entertainment medium. To this end, unless you designate otherwise, the information you enter here will be known to only two parties: you and Clicks Bazaar. We pledge that Clicks Bazaar will not release your personal data to anyone else without your consent - period. You may change the status of whether you wish to receive Clicks Bazaar offers and communications at any time. When we do present information to our advertisers, unless you tell us otherwise, it is in the form of aggregate statistics compiled among all of our visitors' answers to survey questions as well as grouped on-site behavior.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you can contact us at support[@ClicksBazaar.com](mailto:privacy@submitedge.com).

What information does Clicks Bazaar gather/track and how is it used?

    *          Collection and Use of Personal Information.

  *          We collect the following personal information from you.

  *          Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

  *          Billing Information such as billing address

  *          Unique Identifiers such as user name & password

We also collect the following information from you

         Information about your business such as company name, Tel. No. & company email id

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to

         Fulfill your order

         Send you an order confirmation

         Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products

         Send product updates or warranty information

         Respond to customer service requests

         Administer your account

         Send you a newsletter

         Respond to your questions and concerns

         Display content based upon your interests

 **Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.  We may also disclose your personal information

         as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

         when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

         if Clicks Bazaar Technologies Pvt. Ltd. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

         to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

 **PayPal**

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

 **Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider**

Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose.

 **Updating/Accessing/Amending/ Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it] by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support@ClicksBazaar.com](mailto:customercare@submitedge.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

 **Security**

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@ClicksBazaar.com](mailto:security@submitedge.com)  In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

         With whom does Clicks Bazaar share the information it gathers/tracks?

         What is Clicks Bazaar's unsubscribe and data-removal policy?

 **Use of traffic data**

Each time a visitor comes to a Clicks Bazaar Web site, we collect some information to improve the overall quality of the online experience. At Clicks Bazaar content sites, we collect the visitor's domain name (e.g., whether the user is logged on from google.com or Facebook.com), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to a Clicks Bazaar Web site), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Google Chrome browser on a Macintosh platform). The Clicks Bazaar site collects visitor information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement and targeted advertising. We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Clicks Bazaar properties, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but Clicks Bazaar will not disclose your individual identity or personal data without your permission. When Clicks Bazaar does present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

 **Use of cookies**

Clicks Bazaar Web sites may use cookies for internal reporting. Cookies are a standard Internet technology that allow us to both store and retrieve login information on a user's system. Other companies which place advertising on our site also have the ability to assign their cookies to you in a process that Clicks Bazaar does not control. However, cookies cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines, so these advertisers will not know who you are - and Clicks Bazaar will not tell them without your consent.  We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.  Use of Email and URL Addresses Collected from Free Submission or META Tags Generator.  Email and URL addresses used for our free submission and free META Tag generator are logged in a log file for tracking purposes and will not be used to send unsolicited email. The email addresses and URL addresses are forwarded in real time to various search engines via the free submission page. We have made sure in advance that the search engines we submit to do not use this information to send unsolicited email. However, please note that a few of these search engines may send you an auto response, confirming your submission  Use of Email Addresses Collected from Newsletter and Mailing List Subscriptions.  After signing up to receive any of Clicks Bazaar Newsletters or mailing lists by email, users will start receiving newsletters or emails delivered on a daily, weekly, or monthly basis, as well as occasional product-related announcements. Note that every subscriber will go through a double opt-in process to make sure that no one gets subscribed accidentally. After a subscriber signs up on one of our sign up forms a confirmation email will be sent to the subscriber. The subscriber will only be added to our database when they confirm their subscription by replying to this email.  On Clicks Bazaar Web sites that offer newsletters, we collect subscribers' email addresses in order to distribute those newsletters and product-related announcements. In addition, Clicks Bazaar has entered into agreements with a number of other companies to distribute Clicks Bazaar newsletters and mailing lists to users on their systems. Clicks Bazaar newsletters and mailing lists are also offered in a number of Newsletter Partner sites, all of which require a user's email address for distribution. In the case of those email addresses collected by our Partners, email addresses are either forwarded to us for maintenance by Clicks Bazaar, or are kept and maintained exclusively by our Partners under privacy conditions acceptable to Clicks Bazaar. If you are concerned about the privacy policies of a Newsletter Partner site, please contact the webmaster of that site.  Users can choose to unsubscribe from Clicks Bazaar newsletters or product-related announcements at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions found in each email.

 **Use of Data from Paid Submissions or Optimization Services**

All website information provided for our paid submission and optimization services will only be forwarded to search engines, directories and Free For All pages for listing purposes. All credit card information will be kept strictly confidential. Note that to avoid SPAM and unwanted email from automated replies for our 2500+ search engine submission, we will not provide your email address to the engines; instead we will provide them our own email address.  How much time it will take?  It will take 6 days to complete the validation. Please note if error are high it can take longer period of time, our team will get back to you in case of more time required. If you have agreed to allow Clicks Bazaar to make your information available to outside organizations, we will use our reasonably best efforts to ensure that your individual data is no longer distributed by Clicks Bazaar after your removal request. However, Clicks Bazaar is not responsible for the removal of your personal information from third-party lists if you have previously authorized Clicks Bazaar to distribute it.  From time to time, Clicks Bazaar may introduce new products and services to its users. To the extent these new products and services affect this policy, this policy will be updated. You will be informed of these updates and any privacy conditions related to these services.  Changes in this Privacy Statement  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. In case for further clarification please feel free to write to us at [support@ClicksBazaar.com](mailto:support@ClicksBazaar.com) .  Clicks Bazaar, Technologies Pvt. Ltd.,  10777 Westheimer, Suit 1100  Houston, TX 77042.  USA.  Clicks Bazaar, 24, Nand Deep Ind. Estate, Kondivita, Andheri (E), MUMBAI :400059  MAHARASHTRA India

 **** **Additional Policy Information**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

 **Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews**

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

 **Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Merced Systems. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

 **Live Chat**

We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. When you make a request for live assistance, we'll gather information like your name, email id and your message. Any information collected is not shared or used for any form of promotional purposes and is strictly used to respond to customer query.

 **Modification**

Kush Infosystems Pvt. Ltd. as an organization has with it the exclusive right to bring about any modification of the provisions of refund of cancellation policy without intimating prior notice.
